calligraphr.com 2017-09-05

# Calligraphr - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Calligraphr.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Calligraphr.com's purpose in collecting non-personally-identifying information is to better understand how Calligraphr.com's visitors use its website.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Calligraphr.com's websites choose to interact with Calligraphr.com in ways that require Calligraphr.com to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Calligraphr.com gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up to provide an email address. Those who engage in transactions with Calligraphr.com by purchasing an upgrade are asked to provide additional information, including financial information required to process those transactions. However, Calligraphr.com does not store any such information. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Calligraphr.com uses cookies to authenticate users and help Calligraphr.com identify and track visitors, their usage of Calligraphr.com's website, and their website access preferences. 

####  Google Analytics 

Calligraphr uses a Google Universal Analytics cookie for users logged-in to the Applications or the Platforms. Google Analytics cookies do not provide Calligraphr with any Personal Information. Also we do not send personally-identifying information information to Google Analytics. Learn more about [Google Analytics security and privacy principles](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245) and how you can opt out by installing the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

### Business Transfers

If Calligraphr.com, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Calligraphr.com goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Calligraphr.com may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Calligraphr.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and at Calligraphr.com's sole discretion.

Last update: 19.3.2017
